ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4068
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers
1969-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Nelson, Anne
/4068
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
7980443
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3099m: ILR School Proposal for a Working Women's Institute for Research and Education /4015: Barbara Wertheimer Office Files /4053m: ILR School Report on the Off-Campus Labor Relations Credit Programs /4115: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records 5736: Barbara Wertheimer Additional Files 5780/203: ILGWU Jay Mazur Papers
Nelson, Anne; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office
7980443
- 1st New York State Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Albany, NY. July 8-10, 1977
- Affirmative Action for Women - Innovative Programs, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  New York City, NY. January 22, 1975
- Annual AFL-CIO Education Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Silver Spring, MD. March 18-21, 1979
- Barnard College Conference on Special Programs for Women in Higher Education, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Harriman, NY. March 14-16, 1979
- CLUW Conference, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Albany, NY. March 26, 1977
- Commission on Human Rights - Sex (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Contract Negotiation in Private Industry - Preparation and Practice (Box 1, Folder 7)
- East Coast Conference Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Philadelphia, PA. December 8, 1973
- An Elementary Introduction to the History of the Labor Movement in America (Box 1, Folder 9)
- First Buffalo Labor Union Women's Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Buffalo, NY. June 22, 1979
- Founding Conference Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Chicago, IL. March 23-24, 1974
- Michigan Summer School for Women Workers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Ann Arbor, MI. August 8-11, 1974
- Midwest Regional Professional Growth Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  September 25, 1979
- National Board YWCA Regional Administration Consultation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  New York City, NY. June 6, 1974
- National Forum on Women - Strategies for the Decade, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  New York City, NY. November 18, 1975
- New Women's Coalitions: A Working Class Women's Focus, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  New York City, NY. December 12, 1973
- An Order Handbook for Instructors Teaching "The Art of Stewardship" (Box 1, Folder 17)
- OSHA Conference, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  New York City, NY. December 13, 1973
- Problems of Union Administration (Box 1, Folder 19)
- The Professional Employee and His Union (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Professional Women's Caucus Conference, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  New Rochelle, NY. March 2, 1974
- Trade Union Women: A Study of Their Participation in NYC Locals - Local 1199, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- UCLEA Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Columbus, OH. April 2-4, 1975
- UCLEA Conference - University of Connecticut, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  October 8-9, 1974
- UCLEA Conference - University of Wisconsin, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Madison, WI. April 3-6, 1979
- Women and Mathematics - SUNY Albany, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Albany, NY. March 25, 1977
- Women in a Full Employment Economy Conference, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Albany, NY. June 25, 1976
- Women in Management Conference, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Hoboken, NJ. May 20, 1975
- Women's Action Alliance Expo, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  New York City, NY. October 2-3, 1979
- Workshops TWU 552 Flight Attendants, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  October 5+8, 1976
- WOW Conference (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Sessions - 1199 Retirees, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Planning Retiree Counseling for 1199, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Buddy, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Newsletter, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Ellen and Terry's Notes for Handbook, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Handbook Revisions for some later edition, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Handbook Distribution, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agency Corrections of Draft, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Meat Cutters Local 342, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Trade Union Women: A Study of their Participation in NYC Locals - Union Lists folder 1, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Trade Union Women: A Study of their Participation in NYC Locals - Union Lists folder 2, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bridging the Gap: Working Adults and Higher Education Conference - CCNY, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  New York City, NY. September 24, 1981
- The Challenge of the Women's Movement: American Diversity Conference, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  New York City, NY. June 25, 1975
- The Congresswomen's Caucus, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Washington, D. C. March 10, 1981
- The Emerging Needs of Postsecondary Opportunity Programs in New York, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Syracuse, NY. April 14-16, 1975
- First Northeastern School for Union Women - University of Connecticut, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  July 18-23, 1976
- Focus on Women Unionists Conference for Labor Educators, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  New York City, NY. November 14, 1974
- Ford Conference: Research on Blue Collar Women, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  New York City, NY. December 5-6, 1974
- JTPA Conference, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  June 15, 1983
- National Council for Research on Women Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Washington, D. C. April 18-19, 1983
- National University Continuing Education Association 66th Annual Conference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Colorado Springs, CO. April 11-15, 1981
- PEF Summer Conference, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  New York City, NY. August 1983
- Pilot Staff Development Conference - Department for Professional Employees, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Washington, D. C. February 2-4, 1981
- Tenth Anniversary Annual Educational Conference - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  New York City, NY. June 11, 1983
- Trade Union Women: A Study of Their Participation in NYC Locals - Local 22 Dressmakers, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Trade Union Women: A Study of Their Participation in NYC Locals - United Store Workers, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- UCLEA Annual Conference, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Morgantown, WV. March 29-31, 1978
- Wingspread Conference - The Johnson Foundation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Washington, D. C.
- Women at Work Broadcast Awards, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Women in Nontraditional Jobs Conference, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  New York City, NY. October 24, 1974
- Women in the Work Force Conference, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  New York City, NY. January 14-15, 1980
- Women, Work and the Family, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  February 4, 1982
- The Work Ethics and the Changing Roles of Women, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Paramus, NJ. March 21-22, 1974
- AFL-CIO Annual Educational Conference folder 1, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Washington, D. C. Marge 6-9, 1977
- AFL-CIO Annual Educational Conference folder 2, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Washington, D. C. March 6-9, 1977
- Annual AFL-CIO Education Conference folder 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Washington, D. C. March 1-3, 1976
- Annual AFL-CIO Education Conference folder 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Collective Bargaining in the Federal Sector, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Washington, D. C. May 20, 1980
- Contact: A Conference for Women in the Business World, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  White Plains, NY. November 18, 1980
- Cooperative Extension - New York City Programs, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  New York City, NY
- Every Woman's Day: Survival in the 1980's (Box 4, Folder 8)
  New York City, NY. September 13, 1980
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work Advisory Board Meeting, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  May 2, 1980
- Midwest Conference of Union Women Leaders, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Chicago, IL. June 29-30, 1973
- Midwest School for Women Workers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Iowa City, IA. August 24-29, 1980
- National Commission on Working Women, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Albany, NY. April 21, 1979
- National Commission on Working Women Meeting, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Washington, D. C. April 16-17, 1980
- Northeastern Summer School for Union Women, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  New Brunswick, NJ. July 20-25, 1980
- The Northeastern Summer School for Trade Union Women, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  New Brunswick, NJ. December 17, 1982
- Pay Equity Conference, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Washington, D. C. October 24, 1979
- Reaching Higher: A Leadership and Career Development Conference for Women, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Lake Placid, NY. August 27-29, 1982
- Restructuring Work: Alternatives for the '80s Conference, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  New York City, NY. June 11, 1982
- The Schools and Group Identity Consultation, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  New York City, NY. November 7, 1974
- Wider Opportunities for Women, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Rochester, NY. August 5, 1976
- Women and the International World of Work, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  New York City, NY. May 2, 1974
- Women at the Top: Designs for Success Conference, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Briarcliff Manor, NY. December 5-6, 1974
- Women in Apprenticeship Conference, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Washington, D. C. July 17, 1974
- Women in the Work Force Conference, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Women of the USSR and the United States: Issues of Mutual Concern, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Racine, WI. December 1-2, 1979
- Women's Affairs, Civil Rights and Political Action Conference, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Washington, D. C. August 25-27, 1980
- Women's Equity Action League, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  New York City, NY. April 1980
- American Arbitration Association Conference - Women's Rights, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  New York City, NY. February 20, 1974
- Michigan Summer School for Women Workers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Ann Arbor, MI. August 21-24, 1975
- Sixth Annual Women in Industry Conference, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Amityville, NY. April 8-9, 1976
- Women in Trade Unions, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Trade Union Women: A Study of Their Participation in NYC Locals - IUE Local 463, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Trade Union Women: A Study of Their Participation in NYC Locals - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Trade Union Women: Local 1597 - District Council 37 folder 1, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Trade Union Women: Local 1597 - District Council 37 folder 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Trade Union Women: Local 1597 - District Council 37 folder 3, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Trade Union Women: Original Data (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Trade Union Women: Overview Questionnaire Data (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Trade Union Women: Rank and File Questionnaire (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Trade Union Women: Computer (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Trade Union Women: Left Over Questionnaires, Schedules, Letters (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Trade Union Women: Interviews (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Trade Union Women: Attitudinal (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Trade Union Women: Interviews R/F Leaders (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Trade Union Women: Interviews Comments (Box 5, Folder 18)